{
    "subject": "Frederica_of_Baden",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Gustav_IV_Adolf_of_Sweden",
    "human_readable": "Frederica of Baden is married to Gustav IV Adolf of Sweden.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9887189269065857,
            "question": "Was Gustav IV Adolf of Sweden married to Frederica of Baden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.988474428653717,
            "question": "Is there a marriage between Frederica of Baden and Gustav IV Adolf of Sweden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9511929750442505,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Frederica of Baden and Gustav IV Adolf of Sweden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9379357099533081,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Frederica of Baden and Gustav IV Adolf of Sweden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9055666327476501,
            "question": "Who is Frederica of Baden married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8944028615951538,
            "question": "Who was the wife of Gustav IV Adolf of Sweden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8292779922485352,
            "question": "To whom was Frederica of Baden wed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7981133460998535,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the spouse of Gustav IV Adolf of Sweden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7513530254364014,
            "question": "What is the name of Frederica of Baden's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5783180594444275,
            "question": "What is the name of Gustav IV Adolf's spouse?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Frederica of Baden is married to Gustav IV Adolf of Sweden.",
            "html": "yago_24083_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Frederica of Baden's husband?",
            "html": "yago_24083_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the spouse of Gustav IV Adolf of Sweden?",
            "html": "yago_24083_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom was Frederica of Baden wed?",
            "html": "yago_24083_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24083_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24083_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24083_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24083_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24083_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24083_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24083_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24083_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24083_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24083_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. There are multiple mentions of Frederica of Baden being married to King Gustav IV Adolf of Sweden, including the specific date of their marriage (October 1797) and details about their children."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide clear information that supports the statement \"Frederica of Baden is married to Gustav IV Adolf of Sweden.\" Specifically, multiple documents mention their marriage and even provide additional details such as the date (October 6, 1797), location (Stralsund in Swedish Pomerania), and the fact that it was arranged by Gustav IV Adolf himself."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}